(Sheldon:)I don't know about you, but I'm
very uncomfortable with all this.
(Penny:)-Why?
-I've never seen this show before
(Sheldon:)and now I'm starting
with episode 246?
(Sheldon:)It's unnatural.
(Amy:)Just think of the first 245
as the prequel.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Penny:)Okay, shh.
Guys, guys, this is it.
I guess its you and me, kid.
(Mark Harmon on TV:)-What are you doing?
-I'm trying to make peace.
(Mark Harmon on TV:)-We're good.
-Good.
(Penny:)-Are you kidding me?
-What's wrong?
(Penny:)Well, the diner scene.
Where's my diner scene?
(Sheldon:)Don't ask me. Until I see
the prequel, I'm lost.
(Penny:)No, there was supposed to be
a big scene with me and Mark Harmon,
(Penny:)but it's... gone.
(Leonard:)-What happened?
-They must've cut it.
(Leonard:)Oh, Penny.
(Leonard:)I'm... I'm sorry.
(Howard:)-That stinks.
-I'm sure you were great.
(Penny:)This doesn't make any sense.
I mean, I...
(Penny:)I thought I did
a really good job, l...